# **Mahmoud Hweedy**

## Mobile Software Engineer

## Profile

Highly motivated mobile software engineer who is passionate about mobile development, Learning new skills and gaining experience, Intend to build a career with company of high tech environment with skilled, Committed & Dedicated people, which will help me to realize my potential. Willing to work as a key player in challenging and creative environment.

### Education

Bachelor Degree at Computer Science., Mansoura University

09/2014 - 06/2018

## **Professional Experience**

## Senior Software Engineer, Crossworkers

01/2024 - present

• Design and build advanced mobile application

Cairo, Egypt

- · participating in system design
- Participating in writing the CI/CD Pipeline to improve the development process.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features
- Work with outside data sources and APIs
- Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general reliability
- Work on bug fixing and improving application performance
- Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency.

## Senior Flutter Developer, Aphrie

05/2023 - 01/2024

Cairo, Egypt

- participating in system design
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features
- Work with outside data sources and APIs

• Design and build Baddel Mobile application.

- · Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general reliability
- Work on bug fixing and improving application performance

## Flutter Developer, AICTec

09/2021 - 05/2023

• Design and build Agriunion mobile application.

Cairo, Egypt

- participating in system design.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.
- Work with outside data sources and APIs.
- Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general reliability.
- Improved the app design and performance.
- Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency.

## Flutter Developer, Multi-Choice Technology

09/2020 - 2021

Cairo, Egypt

- Design and build ATC mobile application
- · participating in system design
- · Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features
- Work with outside data sources and APIs
- Work on bug fixing and improving application performance
- Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency.

## **Projects**

#### MazAid

Egypt's First Fintech Aggregator.

Baddel is a bike sharing system with multiple stations where you can take a bike from any station and return it at any other station.

I was the only flutter developer among a cross functional team whose goal was to build and deliver the first ebike sharing app in MENA.

IOS 2 Android 2

#### Agriunion

This app digitize the market dynamics of Agricultural crops wholesale market in KSA to move the Agricultural ecosystem into the digital world.

My role was to participate in applying the new design, enhancing the code quality and building new features. Android 🛮

## **ATC Payemnts**

This app manage the transaction process between seller and buyer of Saudi E-vouchers (like: STC, Lebara, PUBG).

I was responsible for all the development activities for the main app and side-apps, for example: building new features, enhancing design of old features, deploying to app stores & custom app stores,

IOS 2 Android 2

#### Others 2

- My Travel: tourist guide app(tickets offers, hotels, etc) IOS ☑ Anroid ☑
- Pharma tree: online pharmacy IOS ♂ Android ♂
- Dokan Omar: online grocery shopping IOS 🗗 Android 🗗
- ☑ One boutique: E-Commerce for cosmetics IOS ☑ Android

## Skills

Agile	
Firebase	• Google APIs
GIT	• Statemanagement
DART	• OOP
3	ilT irebase

## 👣 Languages

• Arabic • English